Henry-Russell Hitchcock
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Chronological Name and Subject Files, 1919-1987, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-22; 21.9 linear ft.)
  Dannatt, Trevor (1952-1953, 1955)
  D'Arcy Galleries (1961)
  Dark, Frank (1955-1958, 1964)
  Darmstadt, Technische Hochschule (1966)
  Darr, William (1956)
  Dartmouth College (1937, 1947, 1968, 1978)
  Darwin, Dana (1957)
  Dauber and Pine (1951, 1958, 1966)
  Davidson, Eugene (1952)
  Davidson, L. (1955)
  Davidson, Rita 1947
  Davidson, W. F. (1952)
  Davies, Jane B. (1957, 1969)
  Davies, Turner and Co. (1946-1947)
  Davis (1959)
  Davis, Dotsie (1984) (see also: Davis, Samuel R. and Dotsie)
  Davis, E. Holden (1969)
  Davis, Elizabeth H. (1953)
  Davis, Howland S. (1948)
  Davis, Laura (1945)
  Davis, Lavinia (1961)
  Davis, Philip and Helen (1927)
  Davis, Richard S. (1950, 1952, 1954-1955, 1957, 1959)
  Davis, Robert G. (1954)
  Davis, Robert Tyler (1948, 1950)
  Davis, Rodman (1983)
  Davis, Samuel R. (1969-1973, 1976, 1978-1979, 1981)
  Davis, Samuel R. and Dotsie (1983) (see also: Davis, Dotsie)
  Davis, Wendell (1945-1946, 1949, 1953-1955, 1958)
  Davis, William (1946, 1955)
  Davison, George W. (1945)
  Davison, Robert (1947)
  Davy Car Hire (1953-1954, 1958)
  Dawes, Horace (1946)
  Dawes House (1954)
  Dawson, Tom (1952-1953)
  Dayton Art Institute (1953)
  De Cordova and Dana Museum and Park (1949)
  De Graaff, Jan (1940)
  De Long, David (1973, 1979-1981, 1983-1984, 1986-1987)
  De Mare, Eric (1956)
  De Sales, Xavier (1956)
  De Vaughan, Carol (1969)
  De Witt, Dennis (1976)
  De Witt, Mrs. Vergil B. (1947)
  De Zurko, Edward R.(1951-1954, 1956-1957, 1959)
  De la Faille, C. A. Baart (1952)
  Dean, Margaret (1951, 1953-1954)
  Dearstyne, Howard (1958-1959, 1972, 1974)
  Deere and Co. (1965)
  Deerfield Academy (1966)
  Deerfield Village (1959)
  Delafield, Mr. and Mrs. Joseph Livingston (1962, 1965)
  Delafield, Lawrence (1965)
  Delafono, John (1952, 1955)
  Delahoyd, Mary (1971)
  Delaney, Beauford (1961)
  Delaware, University of (1957, 1961, 1967, 1970, 1976)
  Delftsch Bouwkundig Studenten Gezelschap (1963)
  Delhaye, Jean (1960)
  Dema, S. J. (1951)
  Demithorne, Janet (1952)
  Democrat Chronicle, Rochester, N.Y. (1936)
  Dendy, William (1975)
  Dening, C.F.W. (1946)
  Department [Smith College Art Department] (1956) (see also: Smith College)
  Department of State (1952) (see also: State Department; United States Department of State)
  Des Grange, Jane (1960)
  Deshmukh, C. D. (1965)
  Design (1957)
  Detroit Institute of Arts (1945, 1959)
  Deul, C. A. (1956)
  Deutsch-Amerikanisches Institut (1963)
  Deutsche Bank (1965, 1967)
  Deutscher Kunstverlag CMBH (1969, 1971)
  Devinoy, Pierre (1948, 1952, 1956)
  Dewald, Ernest (1951)
  Di Blasi, Louise (1962)
  Dick Travel Agency (1945, 1947-1949)
  Dickey, John M. (1973)
  Dickson, Harold E. (1951-1952, 1956)
  Dictionary of American Biography (1955)
  Dictionary of the Arts (1942)
  Dillon, James L. (1956)
  Dillon, Joan (1955)
  Dinan Associates (1982)
  Dingwall, Ronald J. (1947)
  Dinnerstein, Lois (1961)
  Dipsas Booksellers (1950)
  Directory of American Scholars (1963)
  Dix, George (1950)
  Dodd, Mrs. Dexter (1961)
  Dodd, E. Merrick 1961
  Dodd, Eugene M. (1964-1965)
  Dodd, Lamar (1956)
  Dodd, Maurice (1946-1948)
  Dodge Corp. (1954)
  Doesberg, Theo V. (1930)
  Dole, Philip (1962)
  Dolker (1956)
  Doll and Richards (1952)
  Domitilla, O.S.B. (1969)
  Donaldson, James R. (1970)
  Donaldson, Norman V. (1952)
  Donnell, Courtney G. (1972, 1974, 1980-1981)
  Donnelly, Marian C. (1982)
  Donnisfes, Sam (1975)
  Dooley, William G. (1947)
  Dorbey, Margaret (1957)
  Dorfles, Gillo (1956)
  Dormoy, Marie (1956)
  Dorner, Alexander (1938-1939, 1942, 1952, 1954, undated)
  Dorner, Lydia (1953)
  Dorsch, George T. (1971-1972)
  D'Orsi, Juliana (1955)
  D'Orsi, Michael (1953)
  Doubleday and Co. (1955, 1957)
  Douglass Brokerage Corp. (1970)
  Douglass College (1957)
  Dovell, Peter (1954)
  Dover Publications (1962-1963, 1969)
  Dow, Mrs. Frank E. (1952-1954)
  Dow, George (1946)
  Dow, Marian (1950)
  Downing, Antoinette F. (1949)
  Downing, George E. (1961)
  Downing, Mrs. George E. (1970)
  Downs, Arthur Channing (1972, 1974)
  Downtown Gallery (1945)
  Dows, Olin (1941)
  Doyle Stationery (1965-1968, 1972)
  Drake Hotel (1950)
  Drake, Lindsey (1946-1947, 1953)
  Drake, Stuart (1979)
  Drap, Al (1971)
  Drawing Society (1965, 1967-1968, 1971, 1973-1975, 1977)
  Drew, Jane (1946-1949, 1955, 1961)
  Drew, Ralph (1953)
  Drew-Bear, Lotte (1966)
  Drew-Bear, Mrs. Robert (1951)
  Drexler, Arthur (1956-1959, 1962, 1964, 1974, 1987)
  Driscoll, Mrs. Philip (1963, 1964)
  Dublin (1963)
  Dublin Tour (1959)
  Duell, Sloan and Pearce (1941, 1943-1945, 1947-1953, 1955, 1959-1961)
  Duemling, Bob (1951-1955, 1957-1958)
  Duhart, Emilio (1954-1955, 1960)
  Duke University (1962, 1975)
  Duncan, Hugh Dalsiel (1960)
  Duncan of Jordanstone College of Art (1962)
  Duncan, William (1978)
  Duncan, Winston (1979)
  Dunham, Elizabeth W. (1954)
  Dunlap Society (1976-1977)
  Dunn, Esther (1950, 1954)
  Dunn, Helen (1979)
  Dunnell, Mrs. W. W. (1946)
  Dupres, Eddie (1938)
  Durand, Patricia (1956)
  Durham University, School of Architecture (1960)
  Durlacher Brothers (1949, 1951-1952, 1963)
  Dusenberg, Elsbeth (1955)
  Dutch Gables Book [Netherlandish Scrolled Gables...] (1977-1979)
  Dutchess County Department of Planning (1968)
  Dutton and Co. (1965)
  Early, James (1964)
  Early, Marcia A. (1962-1963)
  Early Victorian Architecture in Britain (see: Victorian Paperback)
  East Side Communities, Association of (1976)
  East Sixty-Second Street Association (1970-1972, 1976, 1979)
  Eastbourne Public Libraries and Museum (1946)
  Eastman, L. R. (1960)
  Eaton, Leonard K. (1960, 1968, 1970-1973)
  Ebert, Elizabeth Roberts (1942, 1947)
  Eccles Public Library (1962)
  Ecole des Arts Decoratifs (1956)
  Edgell, G. H. (1953)
  Ediciones 3 (1962)
  Edinburgh Architectural Association (1956)
  Edinburgh, British Council in (1946)
  Edinburgh, City of (1946)
  Edmunds, Sheila (1962-1965)
  Educational Broadcasting Co. (1963)
  Edwards, David J. (1954)
  Edwards, Folke (1954)
  Edwards, Francis, Ltd. (1946)
  Edwards, Jared (1971, 1973-1974)
  Egan, Patricia (1961-1962)
  Egbert, Donald (1945, 1951, 1953, 1956, 1959)
  Eggers, Henry L. (1948)
  Eidelberg, Martin (1969)
  Eisenberg, Marvin (1966)
  Eisenhower, Milton (1952)
  Eisenman, Alvin (1952, 1954)
  Eisenman, Peter (1964, 1976)
  Eisler, Benita (1976)
  Eisler, Colin (1964, 1975)
  Electa Editrice (1968, 1976, 1980)
  Electric Co. (1954)
  Elek, Paul (1945, 1957-1958, 1968, 1970)
  Elkington, Mary (1955-1958)
  Elkington, Robert (1960)
  Ellis, Connie (1969)
  Ellis, Donald G. (1952)
  Ellum, Wendy (1956)
  Ellison, Clifford (1964)
  Elmer, Maud V. (1958, 1962)
  Elmhurst, Dorothy (1937)
  Emery, Ruth (1950-1951, 1954, 1956-1957, 1960-1961, 1968, 1975, 1981)
  Emil, Allan D. (1954)
  Emmons, Mr. and Mrs. Donn (1947)
  Employers Liability Insurance (1940, 1943)
  Enciclopedia del l'Arte (1958)
  Enciclopedia Italiana (1954)
  Encyclopedia Britannica (1955, 1957-1959, 1970-1971) (see also: Britannica Encyclopedia)
  Encyclopedia of World Art (1958, 1961-1964, 1966)
  Encyclopedia Universale Del l'Arte (1969)
  Encyclopedia Universalis (1981)
  Enggass, Robert (1961, 1963)
  England, Robert (1968)
  Engle Lecture (1965)
  Engles, Charles (1948)
  Epler, Robert (1966)
  Erickson, John David (1948)
  Ernst, Barbara (1979)
  Ervin, John (1959, 1961)
  Esherick, Joseph (1954)
  Esposito, Joseph (1977-1978, 1980)
  Essex Institute (1956, 1977)
  Estrada, Rauel (1956)
  Etherington, Edward (1968)
  Etlin, Richard A. (1981)
  Eton College Arts Society (1969)
  Europe (1969, 1977)
  Evans (1965)
  Evans, Allan (1968)
  Evans, David J. (1945)
  Evans, James and Barbara (1952)
  Evans, Janice (1974)
  Evans, John (1950)
  Evans, Kathleen Horne (1961)
  Evans, Lydia (1945, 1968)
  Evans, Rosamund (1945, 1954-1958)
  Evershed, Emily (1966)
  Ewart, Joy (1959)
  Experiment (1963)
  Ezequelle, Betty J. (1972)
  Faber and Faber, Ltd. (1945, 1956)
  Fahertyand Swartwood, Inc. (1970)
  Fairbanks, G. (1946)
  Fairbanks, Jonathan (1960, 1969, 1971-1976, 1980)
  Fairhurst, P. G. (1955-1956)
  Farleigh Dickinson University (1974)
  Faison, S. Lane (1952-1955, 1962-1963, 1969, 1973-1974)
  Fanelli, Giovanni (1969)
  Farley, Margaret (1949)
  Farnsworth, Edith B. (1951-1952)
  Farnsworth, John (1952-1953)
  Farthing, Cecil (1956, 1959)
  Fast-Wengenmayer, Annemarie (1973)
  Faulkner, Jean and Winthrop W. (1956)
  Faulkner, Winthrop W. (1961)
  Feddersen, Phil A. (1951)
  Feder, Kathy S. (1972)
  Feesender, De Witt H. (1953)
  Fehm, Sherwood A. (1969)
  Feinberg, Barry (1957, 1960)
  Feingold, Jessica (1946)
  Feininger, Lyonel (1930)
  Feld, Stuart (1969)
  Feriday, Peter (1964)
  Ferry, Hawkins 1945
  Ferry, W. H. (1947)
  Fiat (1959)
  Fickert Insurance (1965, 1970)
  Fielden F. (1956, 1966)
  Fife Memorial Fund (1951-1952)
  Fifth Avenue Playhouse Group, Inc. (1928)
  Film sur l'art (1957)
  Fine Arts Agents (1946)
  Finkel, Kenneth (1974)
  Finsbury, Metropolitan Borough of (1946)
  Fire Alarm Maintenance Co. (1957)
  First National Bank of Northampton (1952)
  First Presbyterian Church, Baltimore (1939)
  Fischer Fine Arts, Ltd. (1972)
  Fischer, H. R. (1962-1963)
  Fischer, Wend (1974)
  Fischer, Wolfgang (1973, 1980-1981)
  Fisher, Howard T. (1930, 1957, 1976)
  Fisher, Jutto (1962)
  Fishl, Leslie (1960)
  Fisker, Kay (1947-1953, 1956, 1960-1961)
  Fitch, James Marston (1959, 1969, 1972, 1974, 1980)
  Fitz-Gerald, Charles (1951, 1959)
  Fitz-Gerald, Helen Louise (1963, 1966-1967, 1969, 1972, 1978)
  Fitz-Gerald, Norman (1959)
  Fitzgerald, D.V.J. (1971)
  Fitzwilliam Museum (1951)
  Flamm, Roy (1951)
  Flanders, Ralph E. (1950, 1953)
  Fleetwood-Hedreth, Peter (1970)
  Fleming and Co. (1957)
  Fleming, John (1963, 1965, 1969)
  Fletcher Co. (1954)
  Fletcher, J. S. (1924)
  Fletcher, Norman (1951, 1953-1954, 1956-1957)
  Flexner, James (1950)
  Flint, C. (1966)
  Florida State University (1949)
  Florida, University of (1962)
  Floyd, Margaret Henderson (1981)
  Fodera, Leonardo (1960-1961)
  Foeder, Barton (1950)
  Fogel, Seymour (1952)
  Fogg Art Museum (1945, 1948-1949, 1965, 1969, 1974, 1977)
  Foley, Charles H. (1955)
  Foley, J. B. (1963)
  Foley, May E. (1955)
  Fondersmith, John (1977)
  Foote, E. J. (1975)
  Forbes, Astrid and Kip (1975)
  Forbes, John Douglas (1950, 1952, 1957-1958, 1962-1964)
  Force, Juliana (1946)
  Ford, Anne (1967)
  Ford, Charles (1946)
  Ford, Edith (1952-1953)
  Ford, Edsel (1936)
  Ford Foundation (1964)
  Forman, Henry Chandlee (1957)
  Forstman (1970)
  Forstman, Theodore (1969)
  Fort Wayne 1973
  Forum Magazine (1950, 1957-1959)
  Foster, Kathleen A. (1981)
  Foster, Philip (1971-1975, 1978, 1986)
  Foto Hutter (1966)
  Foto Van Ojen (1958)
  Foulkes, William George (1971-1972, 1978, 1986)
  Fourth Avenue Booksellers (1983)
  Foyle Ltd. (1947)
  Franc, Helen (1947, 1951, 1953-1954, 1963, 1977, undated)
  Francastle, Pierre (1956)
  Francis, Dennis Steadman (1978)
  Francis, Francis C. (1928)
  Francis Henry (Harry) Sayles (1925-1932, 1945-1948, 1952-1953, 1955, 1959, 1961, 1963-1964, 1967-1970, 1972-1973, 1977-1981, 1983, undated)
  Frank, Edward (1964-1965)
  Frankbauser, Mary (1966)
  Frankenstein, Alfred (1951)
  Frankenstein, Mrs. Victor S. (1950)
  Franklin, Cecil A. (1961)
  Franklin, Danny (1975)
  Franklin Institute (1963)
  Franklin Square Subscription Agency (1965)
  Franzen, Ulrich (1962)
  Frary, I. T. (1957)
  Frazer, Alfred (1957)
  Fredericks, Mr. and Mrs. Marshall (1952)
  Free Library of Philadelphia (see: Philadelphia, Free Library of)
  Freedman, Harry S. (1952)
  Freeman, Donald (1972, 1976)
  Freeman, Harrison B. (1937)
  Freeman, Judy (1951)
  Freer Gallery (1950)
  Fregna, Roberto (1962)
  Freiburg (1964)
  Freidrich, Reinhard (1964)
  French Line (1970)
  French Railways, Ltd. (1956)
  Frick Art Reference Library 1954
  Friedman, B. H. (1962)
  Friedman, Lee M. (1945)
  Friedsam, M. (1926)
  Friends of the Upper East Side Historic District (1986)
  Frost, Eunice E. (1945, 1950, 1952, 1955)
  Fry, E. Maxwell (1948)
  Fuchs-Greven (1960)
  Fulbright Fellowship (1951, 1959)
  Funk and Wagnall's Encyclopedia (1957)
  Furniture (1968)
  Furry, C. I. (1941)
  Futagawa, Yukio (1974)
  Gaddis, Eugene R. (1982-1984, 1986)
  Gagarin, Judy (1970)
  Gallum, Barbie (1952)
  Gale Research Co. (1964)
  Galecki, Marta McBride (1977)
  Games, Stephen (1983)
  Gardner, Jean McClintock (1983)
  Garfield, Leslie J. (1970, 1973, 1978, 1980-1981, 1984)
  Garland, Peter (1958)
  Garland, Peter and Mary (undated)
  Garland Publishing, Inc. (1975-1977, 1979-1980, 1983-1984)
  Garvan, Anthony N. B. (1948, 1955-1956)
  Garvan, John (1952)
  Garzanti, Aldo (1966)
  Gaston, Godfrey (1952)
  Gaudi, Amigos de (1956)
  Gaudi Exhibition (1957-1958)
  Gaunt, William (1952)
  Gaus, John M. (1948)
  Gayle, Margot (1971-1972, 1983-1984)
  Gazette des Beaux-Arts (1953-1954, 1956)
  Geary, Ronald (1952-1953)
  Gebhard, David (1953, 1966, 1970, 1973-1974, 1977, 1981)
  Gebhardt (1956)
  Geddes, Robert L. (1974, 1981)
  Geer, Ronald (1952)
  Gehring, P. (1954)
  Gelfand, Morris (1947)
  Gelotte, Ernest N. (1954)
  Gemeente Helversum, Publik Werken (1927)
  General Adjustment Bureau (1951)
  Georgia Institute of Technology (1949-1951, 1953-1954, 1962)
  Georgia, University of (1975)
  Gered Antiques, Ltd. (1959)
  German Renaissance Architecture (1972, 1978-1982)
  Germantown Historical Society (1972)
  Gerold, William (1962-1966)
  Gersheim, Helmut (1946, 1953, 1958)
  Gerson, H. (1956, 1958)
  Geske, Norman (1952, 1963-1964)
  Gettier, Astrid E. (1966)
  Getty Trust 1985
  Gibb-Smith, C. H. (1954-1955)
  Gibson, Cynthia (1970)
  Giella, Barbara (1978-1979, 1986)
  Giese, Delius [Fritz] (1948-1949)
  Gift (1956) (see also: Wesleyan University)
  Gilbert, Creighton (1952, 1969, 1972-1975)
  Gilchrist, Agnes (1945, 1951-1952, 1954-1957, 1961, 1968-1969)
  Gilchrist, Brenda (1951-1953, 1957)
  Gilkerson, Ann (1977)
  Gill, Brendan (1970, 1972-1973, 1978, 1980, 1986)
  Gilman's Old Books, Inc. (1947)
  Girauden Photographic (1956)
  Girourd, Mark (1961, 1975, 1983)
  Gisser, Leon (1948)
  Gittes, Lois Severini (1977)
  Glaeser, Ludwig (1978, 1984)
  Glasgow (1966)
  Glasgow School of Architecture Club (1962)
  Glasgow, University of (1967, 1972-1973)
  Glaubiga, Merel (1977)
  Gleason Brothers (1954)
  Glick, William J. (1966)
  Gobel, Laura (1965)
  Goding, Stowell C. (1951)
  Goeschel, Nancy (1969-1970, 1977-1978, 1980)
  Goff, Bruce (1948)
  Goldberg, Gary (1966)
  Goldfinger (1955)
  Goldsmiths and Silversmiths Co. (1946)
  Goldsmith's Hall (1961-1962)
  Goldstein, Malcolm (1979)
  Goldstein, Stanley James (1954)
  Goldthwaite, Richard A. (1970)
  Goldwater, Robert (1965)
  Gomes, Peter S. (1979)
  Gomme, Andor (1963)
  Goodall, Donald (1948-1950)
  Goodall, John (1948, 1952)
  Goodfellow, Gavin (1958)
  Goodhue, H. Shippen (1953-1956, 1958, 1966, 1970, 1972, 1975, 1981-1982)
  Goodhue, H. Shippen and Lydia (1973-1974)
  Goodiery, Susan (1951)
  Goodman, R. (1971)
  Goodrich, Lloyd (1947-1949, 1951)
  Goodspeed's Book Shop (1950-1951)
  Goodwin, Genevive (1965)
  Goodwin, Germaine (1958)
  Goodwin, J. L. (1955)
  Goodwin, James (1966)
  Goodwin, Julie (1979)
  Goodwin, Lubi (1974)
  Goodwin, Philip (1939, 1945, 1947)
  Gorbaty, Norman (1953-1954)
  Gordon, David A. (1977)
  Gordon, Douglas H. (1948, 1952-1953, 1966, 1971)
  Gordon, Rae and Righter Travel (1965-1968)
  Gorski, Taderisz A. (1953)
  Gould, Cecil (1959)
  Gouverneur, Elizabeth (1974)
  Government and Art, Committee on (1950-1951, 1953, 1957)
  Gowan, James (1962)
  Gowans, Alan (1956, 1959-1960, 1962-1963, 1969)
  Graduate Students (1956)
  Grady, James (1956-1961, 1963-1964, 1966-1969)
  Graeffe, Arnold Didier (1947)
  Graf, Otto (1963)
  Graham, F. Lanier (1970)
  Graham Foundation for Advanced Studies in the Fine Arts (1961, 1973, 1978-1979, 1982)
  Graham, Fred (1956)
  Graham, John A. (1945)
  Graham, Roy F. (1977)
  Grannard, Harold (1928)
  Grant, Leland (1975-1982, 1984)
  Graves, Michael (1967)
  Gray, Basil (1961)
  Gray, Christopher (1977-1978, 1982)
  Gray, Nicolete (1958)
  Graybill, Sam (1951-1953, 1957)
  Greater London Council (1985)
  Greek Embassy (1958)
  Green, E.R.R. (1962)
  Green, J. Wilder (1951-1959, 1961-1962, 1977, 1981)
  Green, Priscilla (1952, 1957)
  Green, Samuel (1939, 1945, 1947, 1950-1958, 1960, 1962-1966, 1971, 1977)
  Green, Samuel and Bunnie (1948)
  Greenberg, Allan (1979, 1981)
  Greenthal, Kathryn T. (1977, 1980)
  Gregg Press Ltd. (1968-1969, 1972)
  Gregory, E. C. (1947)
  Grennard, Paul (1928)
  Grey Art Gallery, New York University (1981)
  Greystone Corp. (1962)
  Grierson, Margaret (1952)
  Griffiths, Peter Noyes and Lady (1956)
  Grimes, Tammy (1972-1975, 1977-1979, 1981-1982, 1984)
  Grinberg-Vinavert, Georges (1951)
  Grippe, Peter (1952)
  Grolier Club (1952, 1970-1973)
  Grolier Encyclopedia (1961-1963)
  Gropius House (1986)
  Gropius, Walter (1947, 1950, 1952)
  Grosser, Maurice (1951-1952, 1977, 1986)
  Grove, Elsa Butler (1955)
  Grow, Lawrence (1975)
  Grube, Max (1968)
  Gruen, Victor (1960)
  Guevara, Max and Elisa (1959)
  Guggenheim, Barbara 1976
  Guggenheim Memorial Foundation (1945-1955, 1959-1961, 1963-1965, 1972, 1975-1982)
  Guild for Religious Architecture (1969, 1971-1972)
  Guildford, Glenn (1949-1950, 1958-1959)
  Guildhall (1984)
  Guilloton, Michael A. (1954, 1957)
  Guinness, Desmond (1967)
  Gundermann, Leo (1964)
  Gunther, Nancy (1959)
  Gutheim, Frederick (Fritz) (1946-1947, 1952, 1958-1959, 1965, 1969)
  Gutman, John (1956)
  Guy, James (1949)
  Guy, Rice and Davis (1936, 1938, 1941-1942)
  Guys, Gilbert (1928)
  Haber, Francine (1965-1966)
  Hack, Garrett (1969)
  Hacker (1966)
  Hacker Art Books (1971-1972)
  Hadzi, Molly (1954, 1956, 1966)
  Hadzi, Molly and Dmitri (1955, 1961, 1963)
  Haessler, George (1978)
  Hager, Louise (1956, 1966)
  Hajer, Gerhard (1966)
  Hale, William F. (1982)
  Hall, J. A. (1946)
  Hall, Louise (1948, 1951, 1954)
  Hallmark, Donald Parker (1969)
  Hallsborough Gallery (1965)
  Hambright, Mrs. Joseph (1966)
  Hamburg (1956)
  Hammill and Barker (1947)
  Hamilton, Charles E. (1969)
  Hamilton, George Heard (1945-1950, 1954-1957, 1959-1960, 1965, 1968, 1972, 1980)
  Hamilton, George Heard and Polly (1953)
  Hamilton, Janet (1948)
  Hamilton, Polly (undated)
  Hamlin, Talbot F. (1945-1947, 1950, 1956)
  Hamlyn, Paul (1963-1965, 1967)
  Hammer, Karl (1969)
  Hammond, Caffy (1958, 1961-1963, 1966-1968, 1973-1974)
  Hammond, John (1968-1969)
  Hammond, Walter (1954)
  Hampshire Bookshop (1949-1952, 1960)
  Hanks, David (1977, 1979)
  Hanna, A. J. (1954)
  Hannary, John (1973)
  Hansen, Mr. and Mrs. Preben (1956)
  Hanson, Bernard (1964)
  Harbron, G. Dudley (1946-1949)
  Harcourt, Brace and Co. (1933)
  Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Inc. (1971-1974, 1976-1977, 1979)
  Harday, Jorge A. Ferrari (1969)
  Hardenberg (1924)
  Harling, Robert (1970)
  Harnell and Co. (1967)
  Harper Brothers (1955)
  Harper's Magazine (1945)
  Harrington, Elaine (1985)
  Harrington, Richard (1958)
  Harris Catalog (1968)
  Harris, Eileen (1973)
  Harris, Hamilton (1953)
  Harris, John (1960-1965, 1967-1971, 1973, 1977, 1979-1980, 1983)
  Harris, John and Eileen (1974)
  Harris, Karsten (1972)
  Harris, Margaret (1972)
  Harris, Paul S. (1951)
  Harris, Roger (1961)
  Harris, Tom (1946)
  Harris, Upham and Co. (1955)
  Harrison, M. (1946)
  Harrison, Wallace K. (1953)
  Hartford (1964, 1972)
  Hartford, Huntington (1963)
  Hartford Magazine (1974)
  Hartman, William E. (1962)
  Hartneck, Timothy W. (1979)
  Hartt, Frederick (1956, 1960-1961)
  Harvard Architecture Review (1978)
  Harvard Club (1963)
  Harvard Fund (1947)
  Harvard Magazin e (1978-1979, 1982-1983)
  Harvard University (1923-1924, 1927-1928, 1939, 1942, 1946-1951, 1953-1958, 1961, 1965-1967, 1973-1974, 1976-1979, 1981-1982)
  Harvey, Katharine (1970, 1976)
  Harvey and Lewis (1945)
  Hasbrouck, W. R. (1961, 1963-1964, 1969)
  Hasbrouck, William (1967)
  Haskell, Arthur C. (1955)
  Haskell, Douglas (1945, 1951-1952, 1954-1955, 1958)
  Haskell, Henry C. (1946)
  Haskell, Rosamund (1966)
  Hasler, Charles (1962)
  Hasselmann, Dorothy S. (1945)
  Hatch, J. D. (1948-1949)
  Hatchards Booksellers (1963-1964)
  Hatje, Gerd (1959-1965, 1980)
  Hattis, Phyllis (1966)
  Hauf, Harold (1951)
  Haupt, Otto (1963)
  Hausen, Marika (1965-1966)
  Haverkamp-Bergman, Egbert (1971, 1973)
  Havinden, Ashley (1948, 1952, 1961)
  Havinden, Margaret 1946, 1953
  Havinden, Margaret and Ashley (1950)
  Hawksmoor Committee (1962)
  Hawthorne Books (1979)
  Haydon, Harold (1961)
  Hayes, Bartlett (1954)
  Hayes, Marian (1954-1955, 1959, 1962, 1968, 1970)
  Heath and Co. (1961)
  Heaton, E. W. (1959)
  Hecht, Jean (1956)
  Hecht, Lynn S. (1962-1964, 1966)
  Heckel, Louise (1960)
  Hecksher, Morrison (1970, 1973-1974)
  Hedge, Alice Payne (1948, 1953-1954, 1956, undated)
  Hedge, E. Russell (1959-1963)
  Hedge, Henry R. (1954, 1956-1958)
  Hedge, Mrs. Henry R. (1953)
  Hedge, Mrs. William R. (1947, 1953)
  Hedrich, E. T. (1956)
  Hedrich, J. O. (1969)
  Heil, Bernard (1958)
  Heilkamp, Detlef (1971)
  Heimsath, Clovis B. (1952)
  Heine, Georgette (1970)
  Heintzelman, Arthur W. (1956)
  Heinz, Thomas A. (1978-1981)
  Heinzel, Brigitte (1967, 1969)
  Heiser, Bruce E. (1953-1954)
  Heisner, Beverly F. (1967)
  Held, Mr. and Mrs. Julius (1965)
  Heleniak, Kathryn Moore (1975)
  Helm, Francis and Mary (1948)
  Hemmenway, Mary (1948-1950, 1954)
  Henderson, Pat Milne (1957, 1964) (see also: Milne-Henderson, Pat)
  Henderson, M. (1958)
  Hendricks, Gordon (1967)
  Henley, Helen B. (1941)
  Hennessey, William J. (1975-1977)
  Hennings, John (1955)
  Henry (1973)
  Henry, Anne Wythe (1972, 1975)
  Henry, Barklie [Buzz] (1959)
  Hentrich, Helmut (1957, 1959-1960, 1963-1976, 1978-1981, 1985)
  Hentschel, Walter (1969)
  Herald Tribune (1945)
  Herbert, Gilbert (1970)
  Herget, John T. (1960)
  Hergert, Elizabeth (1963)
  Heron, Patrick (1952-1954, 1956, 1979)
  Herrmann, George (1960)
  Herschman, Judith (1979)
  Hersey, George L. (1959-1963, 1967-1968, 1971-1972, 1975
  Hershberger, Howard (1960, 1961, 1963)
  Herve, Lucien (1956-1957)
  Herzog, Marion Rawles (1967, 1970)
  Hesketh, Peter Fleetwood (1969)
  Hesse (1956)
  Hessler, Herman (1971)
  Heyl, Bernard (1959-1963)
  Hibbard, Don J. (1976)
  Hibbard, Howard (1962, 1968)
  Highest, Gilbert (1954)
  Hill, Draper (1960)
  Hill, Frederick and May (1968)
  Hill, Oliver (1946, 1949, 1955)
  Hiner, Walter (1946)
  Hines, Thomas S. (1967, 1972, 1981)
  Hirschl and Adler Galleries (1968)
  Historic American Buildings Survey (1973)
  Historical Society of Pennsylvania (see: Pennsylvania, Historical Society of) History News (1963)
  Hitchcock, Alice Davis [mother, Mrs. Henry Russell] (1925, 1940, 1942-1943, 1946-1950)
  Hitchcock, Mr. and Mrs. Carl (1955)
  Hitchcock, Charles D. (1940, 1971)
  Hitchcock, Harriet (1963)
  Hitchcock, Dr. and Mrs. Henry Russell [parents] (1928-1929, undated)
  Hitchcock, June (1979-1980)
  Hitchcock, Mrs. Peter S. (1964)
  Hoag, John D. (1952, 1955-1956, 1959, 1961-1965, 1967-1968, 1970-1971, 1976)
  Hochman, Elaine S. (1973, 1976)
  Hodge, Alan (1957)
  Hodge, Philip G. (1951)
  Hodgkinson, Ianthe (1966)
  Hofer, Philip (1945-1947, 1949, 1951-1952, 1959, 1961, 1968)
  Hoffman, Donald L. (1964, 1969-1970, 1978)
  Hoffmann, Werner (1956)
  Hofstra College (1952)
  Hogan, Austin (1940)
  Hojer, Gerhard (1967, 1970, 1973)
  Holcomb, Donald M. 1956
  Holderbaum, James (1962, 1964, 1966, 1968)
  Holdet, L. A. (1946)
  Holdin, Harrison (1976)
  Holiday Inn (1972)
  Holland (1964, 1967)
  Holland-America Line (1958, 1971)
  Holman, William G. (1981)
  Holmegaards Glasvaerk (1960)
  Holmes, J. P. (1953)